okidata.com 2017-11-03

# Privacy Policy Statement | OKI Data Americas

## Policy Effective Beginning: March 15, 1999 Last Updated: September 30, 2015

OKI Data is committed to ensuring the privacy of information provided to us by our customers and visitors. We have developed this Privacy Policy Statement (“Policy”) to provide you with the highest level of assurance of the security and privacy of your information as it pertains to the following sites: www.oki.com/us, my.okidata.com, bpx.okidata.com, and esales.okidata.com (collectively, the “Website”).

This Policy applies to all information collected or submitted on the Website.

Some of your information may be collected and stored automatically through the use of cookies. See below for more information regarding the use of cookies on the Website. 

**Examples of other non-personally identifiable information that the Website collects automatically include:  ** internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We also use WebTrends, LivePersons, Marketo and Google Analytics tracking utilities to analyze user movement and provide general site statistics. 

In addition to the information that we collect automatically, we may also collect information that you provide to us. OKI Data offers various opportunities for visitors to provide information on the Website. This information can be broken down into three main categories.

  1. The first type is personally identifiable information necessary to complete a transaction or purchase, or product return of OKI Data products. This may include such information as name, company name, address, location, phone number, email address, and credit card information.
  2. The second type is optional information to help OKI Data understand the needs and desires of its customers, and in return for which OKI Data may provide the user the opportunity to enter contests and drawings, complete surveys, and/or receive promotional offers or special notifications, among other things. (This may include such information as company size, revenue, purchasing needs, opinions, purchase intentions or history, etc.).
  3. The third type of information is required of registered participants posting information on the OKI Support Forum where selected servicing dealers may exchange information about Oki Data products and services. Dealer personnel participating must provide their full name, title, password, company name, company phone number, service manager name, and service manager phone number as a condition of acceptance; final review and approval of all registrations is reserved by Oki Data. This information is viewable by other registered forum participants and Oki Data personnel. Participants may provide content for the forum. Oki Data will monitor all submissions to the forum and will exercise complete editorial control over all content, which may be then posted in its entirety, in an edited version, or not at all. Participants may also send private emails to other participants including Oki Data personnel. The terms and conditions of the forum are reviewed and accepted prior to participation.

## Use of Information

OKI Data may share personally identifiable information regarding its customers with OKI Electric Inc., partners or other third parties (such as web development partners, PR and Marketing agencies, channel partners, logistics/shipping partners, etc.). However, for these partners or third parties under contract with OKI Data, any individual customer information provided shall be used only to perform or complete a necessary transaction or function related to the customer's purchase or other request or inquiry. These transactions, functions or requests shall be in accordance with the terms of this Policy. OKI Data will not share any individual customer information outside of the contracted partners and third parties mentioned above, without first receiving the individual's prior written approval. In short, OKI Data does not sell registrant information to lists. We reserve the right to disclose your personally-identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. In some cases, OKI Data may use a visitor's personally identifiable information to understand overall patterns for site usage, to contact the user for clarification on inaccurate information, or to follow up on a customer service issue. Personally identifiable information may include name, address, telephone number, IP address, etc. 

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

When a visitor completes any web-based form on the Website, the visitor will be given the opportunity to select whether or not to be included in the OKI Data mailing list and receive promotional messages from OKI Data. Inclusion on the mailing list may entitle the user to receive information or updates about special offers, programs, new products and/or services. Choosing not to complete any web-based form on the Website means the user will not be able to receive these benefits or this information. Additionally, if at any time a user wishes to be removed from future mailings, or change any personally identifiable information on any area of the Website, he or she may send email to [webmaster@okidata.com](mailto:webmaster@okidata.com) or [support@okidata.com](mailto:support@okidata.com). To be removed, type "REMOVE" in the SUBJECT field. To change information, please state existing information and the change requested in the body of the message, or call 1-800-OKIDATA to request the changes be made

## Links to other Sites

This site may contain links to third party web sites that are hosting services or information under the "oki.com" domain or acting as our agents, performing services on our behalf. Any personally identifiable information collected by these third parties will be treated with the same level of privacy and security as that which is collected elsewhere on the Website. 

Meanwhile, links to other web ~~ ~~ sites (outside of the "oki.com" domain) are provided solely as a convenience to you and not as an endorsement by OKI Data of the contents on such third-party web sites. OKI Data has no control over and is not responsible for the content of linked third-party web ~~ ~~ sites and does not make any representations, guarantees or warranties of any products or services of the third party or the content or accuracy of materials on such third party web ~~ ~~ sites. If you decide to access linked third party web ~~ ~~ sites, you do so at your own risk.

## User Control

Customers and visitors who have purchased or registered in the OKI Store at www.oki.com/us/printing, esales.okidata.com, my.okidata.com or bpx.okidata.com, have the ability to change, edit or delete their personally identifiable information online by logging in at the member login page. If OKI Data's privacy policies change in the future and the use of a users' personally identifiable information is used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, OKI Data will post a prominent notice on the Website 30 days prior to such changes going into effect. 

You may also cancel your account at any time by contacting webmaster@okidata.com in writing. If you do choose to cancel your account, the information that you have previously provided to OKI Data may not be available to you should you choose to reactivate your account at a later date.

## Data Integrity

We process personally identifiable information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we collect, store and process only the personally identifiable information needed to conduct an online survey and/or to provide or improve this Website. OKI Data takes every reasonable measure to ensure that the information it gathers from the user is accurate, but we depend on our users to provide accurate personally identifiable information to us.

## Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of the information we collect online, we have put appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures into place to safeguard and secure that information, including SSL – a specialized encryption and security technology. This ensures that your information is safe, secure, and available only to the employees of OKI Data and/or to other authorized users, as determined by OKI Data in accordance with commercially reasonable standards.

## Credit Card Information

Due to the financial nature of the information provided in the OKI Store on this site, OKI Data stores credit card information separately from other contact information gathered elsewhere in the site. This is done as an additional measure of securing your financial information. Because of this, a user may be requested to input some personal or contact information more than once. 

Credit card numbers are used only for processing payments the user requests through this service and are not used for marketing, sales or other purposes. All credit card transactions are handled through an encrypted system with a secure online credit card processing company.

## Dispute Resolution

OKI Data will attempt in good faith to resolve any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to the use of personally identifiable information. Please address any concerns to webmaster@okidata.com who will respond to you within three (3) business days of receipt. We ask that you provide a short explanation of the situation and a return address or phone number where we can reach you during normal business hours.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file containing information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow us to analyze our site traffic patterns and to provide a user-friendly registration and log-in process. A cookie can not give us access to your computer or to information beyond what you provide to us. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. Consult your browser's manual or online help if you want information on restricting or disabling the browser's handling of cookies. 

OKI Data uses cookies to enhance our site and its navigation, in order to customize, personalize and enhance the user experience. For example, by using cookies, OKI Data may be able to present information to the user, based on a specific OKI product they have purchased, or be able to provide only specific information the user requests, based on the preferences they previously indicated when registering. In most places, these cookies are tied to your personally identifiable information. 

Like many web sites, OKI Data may also use pixel tags, also known as beacons, spotlight tags or web bugs, to improve our understanding of site traffic, visitor behavior, and response to promotional campaigns, as a supplement to our server logs and other methods of traffic and response measurement. Pixel tags are sometimes used in conjunction with small Javascript-based applications, also for the purpose of traffic measurement. We may also implement pixel tags provided by other companies, for the same purpose. You can disable pixel tags by changing your browser settings to omit images and disable Javascript; or there are commercial software packages available that can omit pixel tags and most advertisements.

## Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children under the age of 13 is especially important to us. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information on or through our Website from users that we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide any information to us that would or could identify you personally. If you are a parent or guardian and believe that your child under the age of 13 has provided personally identifiable information through this Website, please let us know so that we may use commercially reasonable efforts to remove that information from our systems.

## Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, and/or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Further questions regarding this Policy may be sent to webmaster@okidata.com. 

© Copyright, 2015 Oki Data Americas, Inc., a subsidiary of OKI Data Corporation 

Oki Data Americas, Inc.   
2000 Bishops Gate Blvd.   
Mount Laurel, NJ 08054   
Tel: 800-OKI-DATA
